{
    "subject": "resource/Jules_Van_den_Heuvel",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ghent",
    "human_readable": "Jules Van den Heuvel was born in Ghent.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9827213883399963,
            "question": "Is Ghent the birthplace of Jules Van den Heuvel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9108350872993469,
            "question": "Where was Jules Van den Heuvel born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927548289299011,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Jules Van den Heuvel was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7331197261810303,
            "question": "Can you tell me Jules Van den Heuvel's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747906804084778,
            "question": "What city is associated with Jules Van den Heuvel's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6614768505096436,
            "question": "Where did Jules Van den Heuvel come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6466375589370728,
            "question": "Jules Van den Heuvel's birth city is ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6444455981254578,
            "question": "What city is known for being the birth place of Jules Van den Heuvel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5017846822738647,
            "question": "In which Belgian city did Jules Van den Heuvel originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34659790992736816,
            "question": "Which Belgian city is associated with Jules Van den Heuvel's origins?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jules Van den Heuvel was born in Ghent.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8250_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which Belgian city did Jules Van den Heuvel originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8250_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is known for being the birth place of Jules Van den Heuvel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8250_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jules Van den Heuvel's birth city is ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8250_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8250_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Jules Van den Heuvel was born in Ghent\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that document 1 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8250/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt) mentions \"Famous Birthdays\" and includes a birth announcement with the following text:\n\n\"Jules van den Heuvel, Belgian lawyer, politician (Minister of Justice, 1899-1907), and diplomat (Ambassador to the Vatican, 1915-18), born in Ghent, Belgium (d. 1926)\"\n\nThis information directly supports the triple \"Jules Van den Heuvel was born in Ghent\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Jules van den Heuvel, Belgian lawyer, politician, and diplomat, was born in Ghent, Belgium. This directly supports the statement that Jules Van den Heuvel was born in Ghent."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}